{"1": {"question": "What does the nocturne's association with night relate to?", "correct": "Being performed in the evenings", "incorrect": ["Theme of the idea of night", "Serving royalty in the ranks of knights", "Being a part of a set of works with other themes such as day"]}, "2": {"question": "When did pieces titled notturno first appear?", "correct": "18th century", "incorrect": ["17th century", "19th century", "20th century"]}, "3": {"question": "Bel Canto, an influence on Chopin, translates to 'beautiful singing'. What did this style place an emphasis on?", "correct": "The beauty of the singing voice and its agility and expressiveness", "incorrect": ["The beauty of the singing voice and its regality and power", "The expressiveness of the singing voice and how it can have a loud and full sound", "The annoying opera sound"]}, "4": {"question": "What form is Chopin's Nocturne no.1 in?", "correct": "Ternary", "incorrect": ["Binary", "Sonata", "Consent"]}, "5": {"question": "Which of the following was a distinctive feature of Chopin's notation of the accompaniment pattern?", "correct": "Complex arrangement of stems", "incorrect": ["Basso continuo", "Rhythmic repetition", "Consecutive fifths and octaves"]}, "6": {"question": "What does the tempo designation in nocturne no.1 (cantabile) mean?", "correct": "'In a singing style'", "incorrect": ["'Like song'", "'Smooth and silky'", "'Cantaloupe' aka rockmelon"]}, "7": {"question": "What does 'semplice e tranquillo' mean?", "correct": "Unaffected and calm", "incorrect": ["Simple and tranquil", "Unaffected and tranquil", "Simple and smooth"]}, "8": {"question": "Who are Chopin's Op. 15 set of nocturnes dedicated to?", "correct": "Ferdinand Hiller", "incorrect": ["Franz Liszt", "Heinrich Heine", "Hector Berlioz"]}, "9": {"question": "The term for the extended embellishment that is seen in nocturne no.2 is fioritura, meaning what?", "correct": "Flowering", "incorrect": ["Finishing", "Grand and forte (loud)", "Fortified"]}, "10": {"question": "When were Chopin's No.15 nocturnes published?", "correct": "1834", "incorrect": ["1843", "1934", "1943"]}, "11": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a contemporary of Chopin?", "correct": "Franz Schubert", "incorrect": ["Robert Schumann", "Felix Mendelssohn", "Cesar Franck"]}, "12": {"question": "What nationality was Chopin?", "correct": "Polish", "incorrect": ["French", "Austrian", "Mongolian"]}, "13": {"question": "What was Chopin's primary instrument?", "correct": "Piano", "incorrect": ["Harpsichord", "Flute", "Violin"]}, "14": {"question": "Which of the three nocturnes is the most elaborate, featuring a highly ornamental line for the right hand?", "correct": "No. 2", "incorrect": ["No. 1", "No. 3", "No. 4"]}, "15": {"question": "All of Chopin's compositions include which instrument?", "correct": "Piano", "incorrect": ["Harpsichord", "Flute", "Voice"]}, "16": {"question": "In the last 18 years of his life, Chopin gave only 30 public performances, preferring which setting?", "correct": "The salon", "incorrect": ["The chambers", "The concert hall", "The cathedral"]}, "17": {"question": "What nationality was Chopin's father?", "correct": "French", "incorrect": ["Polish", "German", "Warsawian", "Austro-Hungarian"]}, "18": {"question": "Which instrumental genre did Chopin create?", "correct": "The instrumental ballade", "incorrect": ["The polonaise", "The mazurka", "Music with nationalism"]}, "19": {"question": "What instrument did Chopin begin lessons on in 1823?", "correct": "Organ", "incorrect": ["Piano", "Violin", "Flute"]}, "20": {"question": "What did Chopin study at the Warsaw Conservatory?", "correct": "Music theory, figured bass, and composition", "incorrect": ["Music theory, figured bass, and word painting", "Music theory, composition, and performance", "Music theory, performance, and composition"]}, "21": {"question": "Who composed the Nocturne No 5 in Bb major, H 37?", "correct": "John Field", "incorrect": ["Robert Schumann", "Franz Schubert", "Frederic Chopin"]}, "22": {"question": "To what extent was the Italian opera in the 1830s an influence on Chopin?", "correct": "Striking", "incorrect": ["Great", "Moderate", "Little"]}}